{
    "subject": "resource/Sfakians",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Greek_people",
    "human_readable": "The subject of Sfakians is Greek people.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.6592273712158203,
            "question": "What is unique about Sfakians compared to other Greek groups?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5395851135253906,
            "question": "What nationality are Sfakians?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49253687262535095,
            "question": "Where do Sfakians originate from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4628988206386566,
            "question": "Can you describe the history of Sfakians?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39979663491249084,
            "question": "Where do Sfakians primarily reside?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39258769154548645,
            "question": "Are Sfakians known for any particular cultural traditions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37746500968933105,
            "question": "How has the identity of Sfakians evolved over time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3597649037837982,
            "question": "Are there any famous Sfakians?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20550349354743958,
            "question": "What are some typical food and customs of Sfakians?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16828514635562897,
            "question": "What language do Sfakians typically speak?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of Sfakians is Greek people.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4072_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some typical food and customs of Sfakians?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4072_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous Sfakians?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4072_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How has the identity of Sfakians evolved over time?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4072_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4072_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4072_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4072_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4072_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4072_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4072_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4072_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4072_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4072_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4072_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provided support this triple by mentioning that \"The Sfakians (or Sphakians) are the Greek inhabitants of the region of Sfakia located in western Crete.\" and \"they have been deemed by many who have faced them in battle as courageous warriors\", which implies a strong connection to Greece."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the Sfakians, who are described as the Greek inhabitants of the region of Sfakia in western Crete and their historical and cultural characteristics. This supports the statement that the subject of Sfakians is related to Greek people."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}